<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michalis Titsias</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michalis Titsias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Michalis Titsias is full time Research Scientist at DeepMind based on London, UK. Before he was an Assistant Professor in the department of Informatics at Athens University of Economics and Business (AUEB), and Postdoctoral Researcher at the University of Oxford and University of Manchester. He obtained his Ph.D from University of Edinburgh. He holds an undergraduate Diploma and M.Sc. degree in Computer Science from University of Ioannina, Greece.
Research Interests     Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Reinforcement Learning Continual Learning, Transfer Learning Gaussian Processes, Bayesian Methods MCMC, Variational Inference Stochastic Gradient Estimation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/code/</guid>
      <description>More recent code can be found in the github pages.
Older Code      GLOMO: MATLAB Toolbox for learning layers from video.
  MATLAB software on sampling in Gaussian processes using control variables. Control points algorithm described in the paper: Efficient Sampling for Gaussian Process Inference using Control Variables, NIPS 2009. The software requires the minimize.m function of Carl. Rasmussen.
  Software on sparse variational GPs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>My CV (last updated in 2018) can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>2021    M. Hirt, M. K. Titsias, P. Dellaportas. Entropy-based adaptive Hamiltonian Monte Carlo. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2021.
M. K. Titsias, F. J. R. Ruiz, S. Nikoloutsopoulos and A. Galashov. Information Theoretic Meta Learning with Gaussian Processes. 37th Conference on Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence (UAI), 2021.
F. J. R. Ruiz, M. K. Titsias, T. Cemgil and A. Doucet. Unbiased Gradient Estimation for Variational Auto-Encoders using Coupled Markov Chains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent publications</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/recent_publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/recent_publications/</guid>
      <description>M. Hirt, M. K. Titsias, P. Dellaportas. Entropy-based adaptive Hamiltonian Monte Carlo. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2021.
M. K. Titsias, F. J. R. Ruiz, S. Nikoloutsopoulos and A. Galashov. Information Theoretic Meta Learning with Gaussian Processes. 37th Conference on Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence (UAI), 2021.
F. J. R. Ruiz, M. K. Titsias, T. Cemgil and A. Doucet. Unbiased Gradient Estimation for Variational Auto-Encoders using Coupled Markov Chains. 37th Conference on Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence (UAI), 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/talks/</guid>
      <description>Information Theoretic Meta Learning with Gaussian Processes. UAI (2021).
Functional Regularisation for Continual Learning with Gaussian Processes. Statistics Seminar, Barcelona School of Economics (2020), slides.
Gradient-based Adaptive Markov Chain Monte Carlo. 2th Symposium on Advances in Approximate Bayesian Inference (2019), slides.
Gradient-based Adaptive Markov Chain Monte Carlo. Cambridge University, Department of Engineering (2019).
The Hamming Ball Sampler. 3rd Meeting on Statistics (2015), slides.
Distributed Kernel Representations for Variational Sparse Gaussian Processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses (in Greek) that I thought in Athens University of Economics and Business (AUEB)      Introduction to Computer Programming. (Fall 2015, Fall 2016, Fall 2017)
  Undergraduate Course on Machine Learning. (Spring 2014, Spring 2015, Spring 2016, Fall 2017)
  Postgraduate Course on Machine Learning. (Spring 2013, Spring 2014, Spring 2015, Spring 2016, Spring 2017)
  Artificial Intelligence. (Fall 2014)
  Statistics for Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
