<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Michalis Titsias</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Michalis Titsias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/code/</guid>
      <description>More recent code can be found in the github pages.&#xA;Older Code GLOMO: MATLAB Toolbox for learning layers from video.&#xA;MATLAB software on sampling in Gaussian processes using control variables. Control points algorithm described in the paper: Efficient Sampling for Gaussian Process Inference using Control Variables, NIPS 2009. The software requires the minimize.m function of Carl. Rasmussen.&#xA;Software on sparse variational GPs. The method described in the paper: Variational Learning of Inducing Variables in Sparse Gaussian Processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>My CV can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/</guid>
      <description>2024 J. Shi, K. Han, Z. Wang, A. Doucet, M. K. Titsias. Simplified and Generalized Masked Diffusion for Discrete Data. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.&#xA;A. Galashov, M. K. Titsias, A. György, C. Lyle, R. Pascanu, Y. W. Teh, M. Sahani. Non-Stationary Learning of Neural Networks with Automatic Soft Parameter Reset. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.&#xA;M. K. Titsias, A. Galashov, A. Rannen-Triki, R. Pascanu, Y. W. Teh and J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recent_publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recent_publications/</guid>
      <description>J. Shi, K. Han, Z. Wang, A. Doucet, M. K. Titsias. Simplified and Generalized Masked Diffusion for Discrete Data. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.&#xA;A. Galashov, M. K. Titsias, A. György, C. Lyle, R. Pascanu, Y. W. Teh, M. Sahani. Non-Stationary Learning of Neural Networks with Automatic Soft Parameter Reset. Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.&#xA;M. K. Titsias, A. Galashov, A. Rannen-Triki, R. Pascanu, Y. W. Teh and J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/talks/</guid>
      <description>Information Theoretic Meta Learning with Gaussian Processes. UAI (2021).&#xA;Functional Regularisation for Continual Learning with Gaussian Processes. Statistics Seminar, Barcelona School of Economics (2020), slides.&#xA;Gradient-based Adaptive Markov Chain Monte Carlo. 2th Symposium on Advances in Approximate Bayesian Inference (2019), slides.&#xA;Gradient-based Adaptive Markov Chain Monte Carlo. Cambridge University, Department of Engineering (2019).&#xA;The Hamming Ball Sampler. 3rd Meeting on Statistics (2015), slides.&#xA;Distributed Kernel Representations for Variational Sparse Gaussian Processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses (in Greek) I taught at Athens University of Economics and Business (AUEB) Introduction to Computer Programming. (Fall 2015, Fall 2016, Fall 2017)&#xA;Undergraduate Course on Machine Learning. (Spring 2014, Spring 2015, Spring 2016, Fall 2017)&#xA;Postgraduate Course on Machine Learning. (Spring 2013, Spring 2014, Spring 2015, Spring 2016, Spring 2017)&#xA;Artificial Intelligence. (Fall 2014)&#xA;Statistics for Informatics. (Fall 2012, Fall 2013)&#xA;MATLAB lab courses for Computational Mathematics. (Fall 2012, Fall 2013)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
